// Array of quiz questions, where each object has the following structure:

const questions = [
  {
    // The text of the question
    questionNumber: 1,
    question:'Which company became the first to reach a $2 trillion market cap in 2020?',
    // An array containing the answer options for the question
    options: ["Google", "Apple", "Microsoft", "Amazon"],
    // The correct answer to the question
    answer: 'Apple'
  },

  {
    questionNumber: 2,
    question:'Which African country launched its first satellite into space?',
    options: ["Nigeria", "Egypt", "Ghana", "South Africa"],
    answer: 'Ghana'
  },

  {
    questionNumber: 3,
    question:"When did Twitter announce the 'Super Follows' feature?",
    options: ["2020", "2021", "2019", "2022"],
    answer: '2021'
  },

  {
    questionNumber: 4,
    question:'Which mobile payment service, launched in Kenya, has expanded across Africa?',
    options: ["Paystack", "Flutterwave", "M-Pesa", "Airtel Money"],
    answer: 'M-Pesa'
  },

  {
    questionNumber: 5,
    question:"Which company's CEO announced plans to build a city called 'Starbase' in Texas?",
    options: ["Amazon", "SpaceX", "Tesla", "Blue Origin"],
    answer: 'SpaceX'
  },

  {
    questionNumber: 6,
    question:'What service specializes the Nigerian tech startup Flutterwave in?',
    options: ["Social media", "E-commerce", "Payment processing", "Online education"],
    answer: 'Payment processing'
  },

  {
    questionNumber: 7,
    question:'Which technology is primarily associated with cryptocurrencies like Bitcoin?"',
    options: ["Artificial Intelligence", "Quantum Computing", "Blockchain", "Virtual Reality"],
    answer: 'Blockchain'
  },

  {
    questionNumber: 8,
    question:'As of 2021, which country is leading Africa in tech start-up investments?',
    options: ["South Africa", "Nigeria", "Kenya", "Egypt"],
    answer: 'Nigeria'
  },

  {
    questionNumber: 9,
    question:"What was the major new feature in Apple's iPhone 12, released in 2020?",
    options: ["Foldable screen", "5G capability", "Solar charging", "3D camera"],
    answer: '5G capability'
  },

  {
    questionNumber: 10,
    question:"What is the main purpose of Rwanda's drone delivery service, launched in 2016?",
    options: ["Package delivery", "Medical supply delivery", "Surveillance", "Agricultural monitoring"],
    answer: 'Medical supply delivery'
  }
]